

63-D, Askari 2 Chaklala Scheme 3, Rawalpindi

0332-4472178

faizanullah1999@gmail.com 🔀

designbyfaizi.me

**MATRIC** - SUPERIOR COLLEGE KHARIAN

**2013 - 2015** 921/1050

**INTERMEDIATE - SUPERIOR COLLEGE KHARIAN** 

**2015 - 2017** 791/1050

BS COMPUTER SCIENCE - COMSATS UNIVERSITY ISLAMABAD

2018 - 2022

## **EDUCATION**

I am currently enrolled in Bachelors Computer Science in COMSATS University Islamabad.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

I have worked in **Graphic Design** as a volunteer as well as Lead in different societies and communities in COMSATS University Islamabad, including IEEE, CSS, HULT Prize, Flutter Islamabad, and others.

**Fiverr (2019 - present)**Graphic design & Web development



**DIRECTOR GRAPHICS** - IEEE COMSATS UNIVERSITY ISLAMABAD

2019 - 2020

**DIRECTOR GRAPHICS** - COMPUTER SCIENCE SOCIETY, CUI

2020

**CREATIVE LEAD** - DEVELOPER STUDENT CLUB, CUI

**2020 - PRESENT** 

DESIGN LEAD - FLUTTER ISLAMABAD

2020 - PRESENT

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a Design Enthusiast currently studying CS in COMSATS University Islamabad. I have been creating posters, brochures, flyers, banners for the past 3 years.

I am also a Web Developer and have been working in this field for past year. I am currently Learning Node.JS for backend Development.





# **DESIGN SKILLS**



# **PROGRAMMING/WEB SKILLS**

